(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
みんなー！
Everyone!
24時間配信達成！
24-hour stream achievement!
だけど、だけど、だけど...
But, but, but...
まだあるのよね、ここホロライブにてぺこら24スペシャルライブが残ってるのよ！
There's still more, right? We have the Pekora 24 Special Live here in Hololive!
皆さんのおかげでここまで来れて
I was able to get this far thanks to everyone,
是非ね、ちょっと感謝もたくさんたくさん返したいので
and I really want to give back a lot of gratitude,
やっぱアイドルぺこですからお歌で返していけたらなと思っております。
so as an idol, Peko, I'd like to give back through songs.
そしてゲストさんもたくさんいますのでお楽しみに。
And there are many guests too, so look forward to it.
そして5年目もよろしくお願いいたします。
And please continue to support me in my 5th year.
そしたら早速1曲目から入っていけたらなと思います。
So, let's get right into the first song.
聞いてください。
Please listen.
まわる　まわる　ふたりのフィーリング
Spinning, spinning, our feeling
絡まってる　まわってるハート　キミのせいだよ
Entangled, spinning heart, it's because of you
LoveやLikeじゃ言い足りない
Love or Like isn't enough to say
キミにふわふわしている
I'm feeling fluffy for you
恋愛脳
Love Brain
な、ご重症で辛い　今回もこんなんだ
Wh-, the illness is severe and painful, it's like this again this time
ろくでもない処方箋では　いられない
I can't stay with a useless prescription
は、との重症が舞う　毎回もこんなんだ
H-, the severity of the heart dances, it's like this every time
ほっといたら今日も不規則　アホも重症
If left alone, today is also irregular, even a fool is seriously ill
そっ、それは罠？　キミと出遭った
T- That's a trap? I met you
そこ現実か？　あちらかこちら
Is that reality? There or here
ちょっとま、模試見て　かます愛情に
Wait a bit, look at the mock exam, in the affection I show
どうにかして振り向いて
Somehow, look my way
ワン、ツー、スリーではあらわせない
Can't be expressed with one, two, three
この気持ちの重量さ　は仕様
The weight of this feeling is just how it is
駆け引きワードはわかってんだけど言えない
I know the bargaining words, but I can't say them
言えない　まだ曖昧にしたい
Can't say them, I still want to keep it vague
まわる　まわる　ふたりのフィーリング
Spinning, spinning, our feeling
絡まってる　まわってるハート　キミのせいだよ
Entangled, spinning heart, it's because of you
ショートやデッドじゃ物足りない
Short or dead isn't enough
キミにファンタスティックしたい　I Know You
I want to be fantastic for you, I Know You
まってこれはまだ
Wait, this is still...
なんて言ってもほら
Whatever I say, see...
だって表面じゃまだ
Because on the surface, still...
ほんとは中度の
Actually, it's moderate...
ハート・曖昧性・脳・ハード・バイバイ・ゲー
Heart, ambiguity, brain, hard, bye-bye, game
エブリデイ・妄想・で・この気持ちを・捏造して
Every day, delusions, fabricating these feelings
なんて言っちゃったら　不安丸見えじゃん
If I say that, my anxiety will be exposed
そんなの絶対許しません！　キミだけコソコソ行かせません！
I absolutely won't allow that! I won't let you sneak away alone!
デレてなんかいナイナイよ　気づいたなら即マイマイよ
I'm not being lovey-dovey at all, if you notice, then immediately dance
独り占めしたい　二人きりでいたい　そんなのちっとも思わない
I want you to myself, I want to be alone together, I don't think that at all
全部嘘っていうのは嘘っていうのは嘘で
Saying it's all a lie is a lie is a lie
どうしたらいいの　こんがらがって解けなくて
What should I do? It's all tangled and I can't untie it
ほんとはわかってわかってるよ
Actually, I know, I know
ユー、アンド、ミー、素直（ピュア）おぼつかない
You and me, being honest is shaky
ほどキミとの境界　溶かしたい
I want to melt the boundary with you as much as possible
各・種・まで・エゴって
Each, kind, until, ego-searching
まだ押し倒したい押し倒したい　この求愛本能
Still want to pin you down, pin you down, this courtship instinct
からでまわる　わたしのフィーリング
Empty spinning, my feeling
いま立ってるまわってるハート　かなり痛いけど
The heart that's standing and spinning now, it hurts quite a bit but
だめだ止まれだめ押ししたい
No, stop, I want to give the finishing blow
キミでやまない　ノー、ノー、ユー、ノー、ミー
Won't stop with you, No, No, You Know Me
超えてみせて　ふたりの深層
Show me by going beyond, our depths
恋愛脳
Renai Nou
1, 2, 1, 2, 3 君が好きだよ
1, 2, 1, 2, 3, I love you.
過剰中毒でなおいとおし
Overly addicted, even more lovely
君にファンファーレ 愛ノウ
Fanfare for you, I know love
ずっとファンファーレしたい 恋愛脳
I want to keep playing fanfare, Love-Brain
待って、これはまだ
Wait, this is still...
なんて言ってもほら
Saying whatever, look...
だって表面じゃまだ
Because on the surface, still...
葛藤は重度のご愛嬌
Conflict is a severe charm
無敵の笑顔で荒らすメディア
A media storm with an invincible smile
アイドル
Idol
知りたいその秘密ミステリアス
Wanna know her secret, mysterious
抜けてるところさえ彼女のエリア
Even her flaws are part of her area
完璧で嘘つきな君は
Perfect and a liar, you are
天才的なアイドル様
A genius idol-sama
アイドル
作詞・作曲：Ayase
Idol
Lyrics/Composition: Ayase
今日何食べた？好きな本は？
What did you eat today? What's your favorite book?
遊びに行くならどこに行くの？
Where would you go for fun?
何も食べてない、それは内緒
I haven't eaten anything, that's a secret
何を惹かれても、のらりくらり
Being elusive no matter what's asked
そう淡々と、だけど燦々と
So coolly, yet brilliantly
見えそうで見えない密は蜜の味
Appearing but hidden, the secret is the taste of honey
あれもないないない、これもないないない
Not that, not that, not this, not this
好きなタイプは？相手は？さあ答えて
What's your type? Who's the one? Come on, answer me
「誰かを好きになることなんて私分からなくてさ」
"I don't really know about falling in love with someone"
嘘か本当か知り得ない
Whether it's a lie or truth, no one can know
そんな言葉に、また一人堕ちる
With those words, another one falls
また好きにさせる
Making them love me again
誰もが目を奪われていく
Everyone's eyes are being stolen away
君は完璧で究極のアイドル
You are the perfect and ultimate idol
金輪際現れない
Never to appear again
一番星の生まれ変わり
Reincarnation of the brightest star
その笑顔で愛してるで
With that smile and "I love you"
誰も彼もを虜にしていく
Captivating everyone and anyone
その瞳が、その言葉が
Those eyes, those words
嘘でもそれは完全な愛
Even if it's a lie, it's perfect love
はいはいあの子は特別です
Yes, yes, that girl is special
我々は端からおまけです
We are just extras from the start
お星様の引き立て役Bです
We are supporting role B for the star
すべてがあの子のおかげなわけない
There's no way everything is thanks to her
洒落臭い、妬み嫉妬なんてないわけがない
Annoying, there's no way there isn't envy and jealousy
これはネタじゃないからこそ許せない
Because this isn't a joke, I can't forgive
完璧じゃない君じゃ許せない、自分を許せない
I can't forgive you who isn't perfect, I can't forgive myself
誰よりも強い君以外は認めない
I won't acknowledge anyone but you, who is stronger than anyone
誰もが信じあがめてる
Everyone believes and worships
まさに最強で無敵のアイドル
Truly the strongest and invincible idol
弱点なんて見当たらない
No weaknesses can be found
一番星を宿している
Carrying the brightest star
弱いとこなんて見せちゃダメダメ
Mustn't show any weak points, no, no
知りたくないとこは見せずに
Without showing things people don't want to know
唯一無二じゃなくちゃイヤイヤ
It has to be one and only, no, no
それこそ本物の愛
That is true love
得意の笑顔で沸かすメディア
Stirring up the media with her specialty smile
隠しきるこの秘密だけは
Only this secret must be kept hidden
愛してるって嘘で積むキャリア
Building a career on "I love you" lies
これこそ私なりの愛だ
This is my own kind of love
流れる汗も綺麗なアクア
Even the flowing sweat is beautiful aqua
ルビーを隠したこの瞼
These eyelids that hide rubies
歌い踊り舞う私はマリア
I who sing and dance am Maria
そう嘘はとびきりの愛だ
Yes, lies are an exceptional kind of love
誰かに愛されたことも、誰かのこと愛したことも
Having never been loved by someone, or having never loved someone
ないそんな私の嘘が、いつか本当になること
Such lies of mine, that they will one day come true
信じてる
I believe
いつかきっと全部手に入れる
One day I'll surely get it all
私はそう欲張りなアイドル
I am such a greedy idol
等身大でみんなのこと、ちゃんと愛したいから
Because I want to love everyone properly, at full scale
今日も嘘をつくの
I lie again today
この言葉がいつか本当になる日を願って
Praying for the day these words one day come true
それでもまだ君と君にだけは言えずにいたけど
But still, I hadn't been able to say it only to you and you
あ、やっと言えた
Ah, I finally said it
これは絶対嘘じゃない、愛してる
This is definitely not a lie, I love you
みんなー！
Everyone!
まずは、恋愛脳そしてアイドルの2曲歌わせてもらったぺこ！
First, I sang two songs: Renai Nou and Idol, peko!
どうぺこだったかなー？
How was it, peko?
ちゃんと歌えて踊れてましたぺこでしょうか？
Was I able to sing and dance properly, peko?
そしてみんなのお楽しみ、ゲストパートこのあとすぐぺこ！
And everyone's looking forward to it, the guest part is coming right up, peko!
どんな曲が聞けるかお楽しみにね！
Look forward to hearing what kind of songs!
ってなわけでぺこーらは行ってきまーす！
So, Pekora is heading off!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
電波、電波アップして絶賛感電中
Radio waves, pump up the radio waves, currently getting a rave electrocution
トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
あなたにも　わすれたいこと
There must be things you want to forget too,
かなしいこと　あるのかしらね
Sad things too, I wonder.
知らない映画なのに　涙を流すのは
Even though it's a movie I don't know, the reason I'm shedding tears
ドラマティックが　足りていないからよ
Is because there's not enough drama.
そんな風にも付かないこと
Don't notice things like that,
くだらないこと　考えてばかりね
You're just thinking about silly things.
雨が上がれば　愛もその横顔も
If the rain stops, love and that profile of yours
誰かのものに　なるのでしょう
Will probably belong to someone else.
嘘っぱちの　ファンデーションも全部
Even the fake foundation and all
今夜のため　なのに
Was for tonight, and yet...
一体全体如何して　如何して　何故何ぜハッてな？
How on earth, why, why, why, what, huh?
不安定なカンデラ　何処まで行くの？
Unstable candela, how far will it go?
あなた　一切合切　放り去ってもう
You, just throw everything away already
阿呆じゃ　ないないわ　トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
I'm not a fool, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって　如何にもならないぜ
Even if that time comes, it won't help anything.
曖昧な　本当なんて　メランコリ化
Ambiguous truth just ends up
するだけ　あたしを　さあ攫って　今テイクオンミー　イェー
Becoming melancholy, so take me away now, take on me, yeah
はあ　ちゃんちゃらおかしな　法外っ度かで
Sigh, with such a ridiculous, outrageous degree
食指が　ぴくともしないわ
My appetite doesn't even twitch.
実態の無い感情　放っておいたって
Even if I leave these insubstantial feelings alone,
策略なんて　ありゃせんのに　何故？
There are no schemes, so why?
ああもう　懲り懲りよ
Oh, enough already.
あたしの　喝となる　キッスも
Even my bracing kiss
じっと堪えて　取り付くのってば
I bear it and hold on...
とうとう臨界点
Finally, the critical point.
年がら年中　リップサービス
Lip service all year round
絶感かましては　辟易
Throwing out feelings and getting fed up.
どんがらがっしゃん　フィールガールは
Clattering down, the feel-girl is
涙の目にも　鬼
A demon even in tearful eyes.
今や頭の中の　ミュージックのせいで
Because of the music in my head right now,
あなたの話は　一向に聞き取れない
I can't hear a word you're saying.
少しは真っ当なこと　言ってやりな
Say something decent for a change.
回り出す　ターンテーブル
The turntable starts to spin.
ねえ全部　忘れさせてよ　だけど
Hey, make me forget everything, but...
一体全体如何して　如何して　何故何ぜハッてな？
How on earth, why, why, why, what, huh?
不安定なカンデラ　消えないままで
Unstable candela, without going out...
あなた　一等両舌　言い違ってもう
You, double-tongued, misspoken already
阿呆じゃ　ないないわ　トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
I'm not a fool, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって　如何にもならないぜ
Even if that time comes, it won't help anything.
曖昧な　本当なんて　メランコリ化
Ambiguous truth just ends up
するだけ　あたしを　今
Becoming melancholy, just take me now...
阿呆じゃ　ないないわ　トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
I'm not a fool, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって　如何にもならないぜ
Even if that time comes, it won't help anything.
朦朧な　感情なんて　ランドリーで
Hazy feelings, just wash them
落とすだけ　あたしと　確かめ合って　イエローマジック
Away in the laundry, confirm with me, Yellow Magic.
アイアイヤ　トウキョウ・シャンディ・ランデヴ
Ai-ai-ya, Tokyo Shandy Rendezvous
その時が来たって　如何にもならないぜ
Even if that time comes, it won't help anything.
曖昧な　本当なんて　メランコリ化
Ambiguous truth just ends up
するだけ　あたしを　さあ攫って　今テイクオンミー　イェー
Becoming melancholy, so take me away now, take on me, yeah
そう簡単な祈りだった
It was such a simple prayer
端から段々と消える感嘆
Wonder disappearing bit by bit from the edge
今から緞帳が上がるからな
Because the curtain is about to rise now
静かな会場を後にさよなら
Leaving the quiet venue behind, goodbye
ロウワー
Louwer
言いかけていた事が　一つ消えてまた増えて
One thing I was about to say disappears and another increases
背中に後ろめたさが残る
Remorse remains on my back
従いたい心根を　吐き出さぬように込めて
Packing my heart's desire so I don't spit it out
胸の中が澱のように濁る
The inside of my chest muddies like dregs
受け止めたいことが　自分さえ抱えられず
Things I want to accept, I can't even hold myself
持て余したそれを守っている
I'm protecting what I've left over
霞んだ声はからからに　喉を焼いて埋め尽くす
Hazy voice is parched, burning my throat and filling it up
何を言うべきか分からなくて
I don't know what I should say
感じてたものが　遠く放たれていた
The things I was feeling were released far away
同じようで違うんだかちか
Is it the same or is it different, the value
何時まで行こうか
Until when shall we go?
何処まで行けるのか
How far can we go?
定かじゃないなら何を想うの
If it's not certain, what do you think?
僕らが離れるなら
If we are to part
僕らが迷うなら
If we are to wander
その度に何回も　繋がれる様に
So that we can be connected many times over
ここに居てくれるなら
If you can stay here
離さずにいられたら
If we could stay together without letting go
まだ誰も知らない　感覚で救われていく
We'll be saved by a sensation that no one knows yet
ロウワー
LOUWER
平穏とは消耗を以て代わりに成す
Peace is achieved through exhaustion in exchange
実際はどうも変わりはなく
In reality, nothing much changes
享楽とは嘘で成る
Pleasure is made of lies
綻ぶ前にここを出て行こうか
Shall we get out of here before it unravels?
と都合の良い願いを
Such a convenient wish
同じ様に同じ様に呟く
I whisper the same thing over and over
何処から聞こうか
From where shall I listen?
何を見失うか
What will I lose sight of?
定かじゃないから此処を動けない
Because it's uncertain, I can't move from here
僕らが疲れるなら
If we get tired
これ以上無いなら
If there's nothing more
その度に何回も逃げ出せる様に
So that we can escape time and time again
心が守れる様に
So that our hearts can be protected
奪われない様に
So they won't be stolen
互いに託して
Entrusting each other
身体を預けてよ
Entrust your body to me
君と泣く
Crying with you
君と笑う
Laughing with you
君と怒る
Getting angry with you
君と歌う
Singing with you
君と踊る
Dancing with you
君と話す
Talking with you
いつまで続くだろうと
Wondering how long it will continue
同じ様に同じ様に呟く
I whisper the same thing over and over
いま忘れないよう刻まれた空気を
The atmosphere carved so as not to be forgotten now
これから何度思い出すのだろう
How many times will I remember it from now on?
僕らだけが
Only we
離れるなら
If we separate
迷うなら
If we get lost
その度に何回も繋がれる様に
So that we can be connected time and time again
ここに居てくれるなら
If you'll stay here
離さず居られたら
If we could stay together without letting go
まだ誰も知らない感覚で
With a sensation that no one knows yet
僕の
My...
生きてるすべてを
Everything I'm living
確かめて正しくして
Confirm it and make it right
Ah...
サンドリヨン
作詞：orange / 作曲：Dios/シグナルP
Sandrion
Lyrics: orange / Composition: Dios/Signal-P
朝まで踊る夢だけ見せて
Just let me dream of dancing until morning
時計の鐘が解く魔法を
Of the magic that the clock's chime will undo
曖昧な指 誘う階段
Indistinct fingers, the inviting stairs
三段飛ばしに跳ねていく
Leaping up three steps at a time
馬車の中で震えていた
I was trembling inside the carriage
みじめな古着
My wretched old clothes...
めくりめくれ夜の舞踏会
Reveal and transform at the night's ball
見知らぬ顔探す 囁くあの声が
Searching for an unfamiliar face, that whispering voice...
握り締めた刃 突き立て
Plunge the blade you've gripped tight
全てを奪えと
And steal everything
孤児集う城 笑み仮面に描いて
In the castle where orphans gather, painting a smiling mask
偽りの慈しみさえ
Even the false affection...
羽で包むセラフ
A seraph wrapping it in wings
灰の中で赤く溶けて混じる
Melting and mixing red within the ashes
ガラスの靴
The glass slippers
今更帰る 震えているの
Returning now, are you trembling?
あなたが目をやる時計
The clock you glance at
靴脱ぎ踊る スロープ抜けて
Taking off slippers and dancing, through the slope
喉まで伸びる指の先で
With the fingertips reaching up to the throat
すくう雫
The scooped-up droplets...
口付けて
Seal it with a kiss
走る衝動 背骨抜けてゆく
The racing impulse surges through the spine
刹那
In an instant
鐘は鳴らさないで あなたにひざまずき
Don't let the bells toll, kneeling before you
まだだめとささやいた
I whispered, "Not yet"
震える右手が...
My trembling right hand...
突き刺すサヨナラ...
Piercing goodbye...
消せない証言を...
Indelible testimony...
交わす陰に纏う姫
Princess wearing the shadows of an exchange
強い瞳 僕を請うた...
Strong eyes, you asked for me...
仮面ごと 打ち抜く...
Piercing even through the mask...
今も耳に あなたの吐息が...
Even now, your breath is in my ears...
突き刺さるの...
It pierces me...
遠い夢...
A distant dream...
澄んで落くらす...
Living in clarity...
慈悲光る月が...
The mercy-shining moon...
君に被せたベール...
The veil it placed over you...
ドレス膝で裂いて...
Tearing the dress at the knees...
ティアラ投げ捨てて...
Throwing away the tiara...
見つめ合う瞳と瞳が...
Eyes meet eyes...
火花を放つ...
And sparks fly...
孤独な魂が...
Lonely souls...
炎上げ 惹かれあう...
Rising in flames, attracted to each other...
その涙 救えないなら...
If I can't save those tears...
まるで独り...
As if alone...
遊びよく まれ今は...
Playing well, for now...
あなたに酔いしれて...
I'm intoxicated by you...
揺れる鼓動 ひとつひとつを...
Every single trembling heartbeat...
刻みつけていたい...
I want to engrave them...
とどまるほど 熱く濡れ...
Wet with heat enough to stop time...
打ち付ける高鳴りに...
To the pounding excitement...
これ以上は動けないよ...
I can't move any more...
まるで停まっている...
As if standing still...
だいしきゅーだいしゅき
Extremely Urgent, I Love You
作詞・作曲：佐々木喫茶
Lyrics & Composition: Sasaki Kissa
One, two, Get you, 熱々 One, two...
One, two, Get you, hot One, two...
シュキシュキではじけた Be my...
Shuki shuki, it popped, Be my...
ルーレット ドキドキ スタート ゲット!
Roulette heartbeat start get!
イタイタイタイ...
It hurts, hurts, hurts...
A-cute, Thank you, トキメキのQ...
A-cute, Thank you, heartbeat Q...
1ミリの隙間にタイビング
Diving into a 1mm gap
ラブスタンプ全部コンプしてアップ
Love stamps all completed and up
イタイタイタイして
Hurting, hurting, hurting
せーの!
Ready, go!
だって今日はゴッドメンタル
Because today is God Mental
勇ましきチャレンジャー
A brave challenger
ちょっとだけセンチメンタル
Just a little sentimental
だいしきゅーだいしゅき 1, 2, 3, ハイ!
Extremely Urgent, I Love You! 1, 2, 3, Go!
めみむめも めもめも 見れないの...
Memimumemo, memo memo, I can't look...
だちづでと でとでと 手が触れて...
Dachizudeto, deto deto, hands touching...
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ!
Become 'Extremely Urgent, I Love You'!
もっと キュッキュッキュッ と強制ラブ!
More Kyu-kyu-kyu and forced love!
あのね クリおね 透けてるハート
You know, clione, a transparent heart
でもね この胸 見透かさないで
But don't look through this heart
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ!
Become 'Extremely Urgent, I Love You'!
アタシじゃないなんて 終わってんね
If it's not me, you're finished
One, two, Get you, ミツケツ One, two...
One, two, Get you, Mitsuketsu One, two...
シュキシュキでカラフル Cutie mind...
Shuki shuki and colorful cutie mind...
ルーレット ちょっと ストップ いたキュー!
Roulette, wait, stop, urgent!
シアワセでも せーの!
Even if happy, ready, go!
だって今日は求めてる
Because today I'm seeking
麗しきチャレンジャー
A beautiful challenger
ハート描いたオートメーション
Heart-drawn automation
だいしきゅーだいしゅき 1, 2, 3, ハイ!
Extremely Urgent, I Love You! 1, 2, 3, Go!
めみむめろ めろめろにしてほしいの...
Memimumero, melo melo, I want you to make me...
なにぬねこ ねこねこ 恋のコネクター
Naninuneko, neko neko, connector of love
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ!
Become 'Extremely Urgent, I Love You'!
もっと キッキッキッ と強制ラブ!
More Ki-ki-ki and forced love!
あのね マリオね あやつらレイディー
You know, Mario, manipulated lady
でもね それもね 悪くはないね
But that's not bad either
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ!
Become 'Extremely Urgent, I Love You'!
アタシじゃないなんて 終わってんね
If it's not me, you're finished
フレンドリーなフリして...
Pretending to be friendly...
周波数を乱さないで...
Don't disturb the frequency...
いわくつきの魅惑のリップ...
Seductive lips with a backstory...
リアルになる be love...
Becoming real, be love...
めみむめも めもめも 見れないの...
Memimumemo, memo memo, I can't look...
だちづでと でとでと 手が触れて...
Dachizudeto, deto deto, hands touching...
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ!
Become 'Extremely Urgent, I Love You'!
もっと キュッキュッキュッ と強制ラブ!
More Kyu-kyu-kyu and forced love!
あのね クリおね 透けてるハート
You know, clione, a transparent heart
でもね この胸 見透かさないで
But don't look through this heart
だいしきゅーだいしゅきになれ!
Become 'Extremely Urgent, I Love You'!
アタシじゃないなんて 終わってんね
If it's not me, you're finished
だいしゅきーだいしゅきになれ！
Become totally in love, in love!
アタシじゃないなんて
Thinking it's not me...
終わってんねー！
It's so over!
まみむめもめもめも見れないの
Ma-mi-mu-me-mo, I can't even look at you
たちつてとてとてと手が触れて
Ta-chi-tsu-te-to, our hands touch
だいしゅきーだいしゅきになれ！
Become totally in love, in love!
もっとキュキュキュキュ強制ラブ！
More squeak-squeak-squeak-squeak, forced love!
あの目くりおね　つけてるハート
Those Clione eyes, wearing a heart
でもねこの胸　見透かさないで
But hey, don't see right through my heart
だいしゅきーだいしゅきになれ！
Become totally in love, in love!
アタシじゃないなんて
Thinking it's not me...
終わってんねー！
It's so over!
Happiness
Yeah Yeah Yeah...
向かい風の中で
In the headwind
嘆いてるよりも
Rather than lamenting
上手く行く事を
Thinking things will go well
想像すれば
If you imagine it
いつか
Someday
変わる時がくる
The time to change will come
夢中で生きてたら
If you live with all your might
何気ない事で
By something casual
愛が傷ついて
Love gets hurt
ためらいながら
While hesitating
何度も立ち上がるよ
You stand up again and again
思い出の後先を
The aftermath of memories
考えたら
When I think about it
寂しすぎるね
It's too lonely
騒がしい未来が
A noisy future
向こうで
Over there
きっと待ってるから
Is surely waiting
走り出せ　走り出せ
Start running, start running
明日を迎えに行こう
Let's go meet tomorrow
君だけの音を聞かせてよ
Let me hear only your sound
全部感じてるよ
I'm feeling it all
止めないで　止めないで
Don't stop, don't stop
今を動かす気持ち
The feeling that moves the present
どんなに小さなつぼみでも
No matter how small the bud
一つだけのHappiness
The one and only Happiness
涙の気持ちさえ
Even the feeling of tears
言葉にできない
Cannot be put into words
幸せの虹は
The rainbow of happiness
何色なんてもう
What color it is
気にしなくていいから
You don't have to care anymore
答えを見つけようと
Trying to find the answer
思い出また
Memories again
積み重ねてる
Are piling up
ここから
From here
新しい場所へ
To a new place
何も恐れないで
Without fearing anything
遠くまで　遠くまで
Far away, far away
どこまでも続く道
The road that continues forever
君だけの声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear only your voice
ずっと側にいるよ
I'll always be by your side
止めないで　止めないで
Don't stop, don't stop
ずっと信じる気持ち
The feeling of always believing
今は名もないつぼみだけど
It's a nameless bud for now, but...
一つだけのHappiness
The one and only Happiness
走り出せ　走り出せ
Start running, start running
明日を迎えに行こう
Let's go meet tomorrow
君だけの音を聞かせてよ
Let me hear only your sound
全部感じてるよ
I'm feeling it all
止めないで　止めないで
Don't stop, don't stop
今を動かす気持ち
The feeling that moves the present
どんなに小さなつぼみでも
No matter how small the bud
一つだけのHappiness
The one and only Happiness
Yeah Yeah Yeah...
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah...
みんな、みんな、まだ！まだ終わってねえぺこだよ！
Everyone, everyone, not yet! It's not over yet, peko!
ちょっとここから、ぺこらのお知らせタイム！
From here, it's Pekora's announcement time!
まあ多分、気づいてる人もいるとは思いますぺこですけども、
Well, I think some people might have noticed, peko,
まあぺこらも4周年となったので、
since Pekora has reached her 4th anniversary,
今回も出ますよ！4周年記念グッズ！
This time too, they're coming out! 4th Anniversary Commemorative Goods!
紹介していきたいと思うぺこです！
I'd like to introduce them, peko!
うさだぺこら活動4周年記念グッズのこちらでございます！
These are the Usada Pekora 4th Anniversary Commemorative Goods!
1つ目はこちら！トゥルルン！
The first one is this! Ta-da!
ラバーマット！
Rubber Mat!
こちらですね、なんと、
This one, would you believe it,
はぐれママ描き下ろしのラバーマットとなっております！
is a rubber mat with a new illustration by Hagure-mama!
うさだぺこらの色んな衣装が書いてあって可愛いぺこですよね！ぜひ使ってくださいぺこ！
It features Usada Pekora in various outfits, so it's very cute, peko! Please use it, peko!
ぺこらと一緒に、お揃いにしてもらえたらなと思うぺこ！
I hope you can get one to match with Pekora, peko!
そして続いてはこちら！トゥルルン！
And moving on, the next one is this! Ta-da!
さかきやひろ先生描き下ろしの、アクリルスタンド！イェーイ！
An acrylic stand with a new illustration by Sakaki Yahiro-sensei! Yay!
今までさ、ぺこら多分だけど、
Up until now, Pekora thinks, anyway,
まあ公式とかのアクリルとかはあったけど、
there were official acrylics and stuff,
新3Dの衣装のアクリルスタンドは初めて出すぺこですので、
but this is the first time I'm releasing an acrylic stand in the new 3D outfit, peko.
今回が初ぺこですよ！しかも、普通のアクリルスタンドじゃない！
So this is a first, peko! What's more, it's not just an ordinary acrylic stand!
ホログラム加工付きのキラキラしたアクリルスタンドぺこですので、
It's a sparkly acrylic stand with a hologram finish, peko.
ぜひお部屋に1個置いてもいいのかなと思いますので、よろしくお願いしますぺこ！
So I think it would be nice to have one in your room. Please check it out, peko!
続いてはこちら！トゥルルン！
Moving on, here's the next one! Ta-da!
タンブラー！
Tumbler!
やっぱさ、配信には飲み物！
After all, you need a drink for streaming!
みんなのお供に1つタンブラー、必要ぺこかなと思いまして、
I thought everyone might need a tumbler as a companion, peko.
ぜひね、この可愛いタンブラーを持ってぺこらの配信に、
So, by all means, please take this cute tumbler and come to Pekora's streams,
これからもね、来ていただきたいということでタンブラー作ってみました！
from now on as well! That's why I made this tumbler!
そして最後はこちら！
And finally, this one!
うさだぺこらぬいぐるみ！
Usada Pekora Plushie!
可愛くないぺこですか？
Isn't it cute, peko?
めちゃめちゃ可愛く作っていただいております！
They've made it incredibly cute!
まあね、結構もうね、ぬいぐるみとかは出てたりもするぺこですけど、
Well, quite a few plushies have been released already, peko,
ぺこらからちゃんと出すのは初めてなので、
but this is the first time one is being officially released from Pekora herself,
ぜひたくさんぬいぐるみいっぱい置いちゃってね、
so please get lots of plushies and place them everywhere,
一緒にぺこらとともに過ごしてるんだっていう感じで、
to feel like you're spending time together with Pekora.
思っていただきたいぺこですので、もう1個とは言わずたくさん、
That's what I'd like you to feel, peko, so don't just stop at one, get many!
一緒にぺこちゃんと寝ていただけたらなとも思うし、
I hope you can sleep together with Peko-chan,
お部屋にね、飾るだけでもいいぺこだし、
or just decorating your room with them is fine too, peko.
あの旅行とかにも連れてってあげたりとか、
You can also take them with you on trips and such.
たくさん使い道があると思うぺこですので、
There are many ways to enjoy them, peko.
ぜひお手元によろしくお願いしますぺこ！
So please do get your hands on one, peko!
そしてこちら、フルセット特典がございます！
And there's also a full set bonus!
ちょっとね、数量限定の特典には、
For the limited edition bonus,
ぺこら、また書きます！直筆サイン！
Pekora will be writing them again! Hand-signed autographs!
そして箔押しの複製メッセージ入り！
And it includes a foil-stamped duplicated message!
こちらははぐれ先生の描き下ろしポストカード！
This is a postcard with a new illustration by Hagure-sensei!
そして通常は箔押しの複製サインがあります！
And the regular version has a foil-stamped duplicated signature!
そして、このフルセットの特典ボイス！
And, the bonus voice for this full set!
ぺこらの気持ちを伝えたいボイス！
A voice where I want to convey Pekora's feelings!
なんなんだ？気になるよな！
What is it? You're curious, right?
ぺこらが何の気持ちを伝えたいのか、
What kind of feelings Pekora wants to convey...
罵倒なのか、それとも感謝なのか、
Whether it's verbal abuse, or perhaps gratitude,
わからないぺこだけど、聞きたい人はぜひ！
I don't know, peko, but if you want to hear it, by all means!
よろしくお願いしますぺこ！
Please check it out, peko!
ぺこらの思いを込めたぺこですので、
It's filled with Pekora's thoughts, peko,
まあこれを機に何かぺこらのことを知りたい、
so if you want to take this opportunity to learn something about Pekora,
気持ちが分かりたい人はぜひ買っていただきたいなと、いうふうに思います！
or if you want to understand my feelings, please do buy it, is what I'm thinking!
本当にね、可愛い4つのねグッズなので、ぜひとも、
They're really four cute items, so please,
お求めいただけたらなと思うぺこ！
I hope you consider purchasing them, peko!
グッズはこんな感じぺこですかね。
I guess that's it for the goods, peko.
そして本当に4周年、いやもう、
And really, the 4th anniversary... no, wait,
次から5周年目？5年目か。5年目になるうさだぺこら。
from now on it's the 5th anniversary? The 5th year. Usada Pekora entering her 5th year.
ちょっと4周年はちょっと24時間という、
For the 4th anniversary, I did a 24-hour stream,
今までにない試み、そして最後にはスペシャルライブという、
an unprecedented challenge, followed by a special live at the end.
いやもう、みんな眠くになってないぺこか？
I mean, isn't everyone getting sleepy, peko?
大丈夫？もうちょっとあるからね！
Are you okay? There's still a little bit left!
そしてこれからも5年目もね、一緒にぺこラストーリーを、
And from now on, in the 5th year too, let's walk the Pekora story together,
歩んでいっていただけたらなと思うぺこ！
I hope you'll continue to walk with me, peko!
そしてこの後は、最後に4周年やって、4年やって、
And after this, finally, having reached the 4th anniversary, having done this for 4 years...
ほら、他にもオリソンがね、ありますぺこですよね。
Look, there are other original songs too, right?
何曲あるか覚えてますか？ 何曲あるか。
Do you remember how many there are? How many...
これから、兎田ぺこらオリソンメドレーを最後に披露したいなと思います！
Now, to finish off, I'd like to perform the Usada Pekora Original Song Medley!
最後までみんな、ちゃんと聞いとけぺこだよ。
Everyone, make sure you listen well until the very end.
それじゃあ、準備してきます！バイバーイ！
Well then, I'm going to go get ready! Bye-bye!
ぺこらんだむぶれいん！
作詞 畑 亜貴 作曲 俊龍
Pekorandaumurein!
Lyrics: Aki Hata, Music: Shunryu
らんだむぶれいんわおっ
Random Brain, wow!
叫んじゃえわおっ
Let's scream it out, wow!
事件だ
It's an incident!
毎日大変
Every day is a struggle!
大成功のタネだと
As the seeds of great success...
笑えない 泣いちゃうな 笑え！
Can't laugh, don't cry, just laugh!
ぺこらっ ぷにんぷにんぷにんと
Pekora, punin punin punin...
ぺこっ ぺんっ だむしちゃえだまえ
Peko, pen, damushichae-damae
NO NO NO の指令 無視返せそりゃ
No, no, no orders, just ignore them and give them back!
NO NO NO の指令 らんだむだ Random! Random!
No, no, no orders, it's random! Random! Random!
NO NO NO の指令 無視返せそりゃ
No, no, no orders, just ignore them and give them back!
受け取り拒否れるぞ！
You can refuse to accept them!
なんだ意外な
What a surprise!
たっちゃんごー
Tatchan-go!
ぴゅんだプロペラ回せ
Zooming, spin the propeller!
どこへ向かうか知らない
I don't know where it's going!
知らないんだ
I really don't know!
なんと世界は繋がっちゃ
Somehow the world gets connected!
きょいとどこかへ銀河系
And zoom, off somewhere into the galaxy!
誰に会いたいって思うんだ
Who do you want to meet?
そんなのどうでも
That doesn't really matter...
いいじゃいじゃん
Isn't that just fine?
退屈イヤだったら
If you're bored and hate it...
こっち来れば？
...why not come over here?
大事な場所なんてさ
An important place...
自分で作らなくちゃ
...you have to make it yourself.
これぞ
This is it!
ぺきょだ どだ どだ どだ
It's Pekyo! How is it, how is it, how is it!
ありがた迷惑か？
Is it an unwelcome favor?
らんだむぶれいんびっくりだわおっ
Random Brain, what a surprise, wow!
生きてりゃ 毎日大変
As long as you're alive, every day is a struggle!
大問題のあとには
After a big problem...
楽しいことあるから
...something fun will happen!
らんだむぶれいんわおっ
Random Brain, wow!
叫んじゃえわおっ
Let's scream it out, wow!
事件だ
It's an incident!
毎日大変
Every day is a struggle!
大成功のタネだと
As the seeds of great success...
笑えない 泣いちゃうな 笑え！
Can't laugh, don't cry, just laugh!
ぺこらっ ぷにんぷにんぷにんと
Pekora, punin punin punin...
ぺこっ ぺんっ だむしちゃえだまえ
Peko, pen, damushichae-damae
NO NO NO の指令 無視返せそりゃ
No, no, no orders, just ignore them and give them back!
NO NO NO の指令 らんだむだ Random! Random!
No, no, no orders, it's random! Random! Random!
NO NO NO の指令 無視返せそりゃ
No, no, no orders, just ignore them and give them back!
受け取り拒否れるぞ！
You can refuse to accept them!
どっちが好きなのよ
Which one do you like?
いいわけバニー
作詞 見里 瑞樹 作曲 ナナホシ管弦楽団
Iiwake Bunny
Lyrics: Mizuki Misato, Music: Nanahoshi Orchestra
なんとか ならないかな
Can't something be done about this?
隣のアイツが邪魔だなぁ
The guy next to me is such a nuisance.
先制必勝！絶対！
Win by striking first! Absolutely!
とわとわ 違うな なんだって競争
Towa-towa, that's not it, everything's a competition.
苦手だ そういうの
I'm not good at that kind of thing.
なんだか 寂しい気持ちは ちまちま
Somehow, these lonely feelings are small.
LET ME SHOW！ しーくれっと
LET ME SHOW! Secret!
あの子に負けない気分だってジェラシー
I won't lose to that girl, even if I feel jealous.
言わなくたって わかってる
I know, even without being told.
あーでもない こーでもない やめにしましょう
Let's stop with the 'not this, not that' already.
貫け MY MY MY
Push through, MY MY MY!
聞きたくない！いいわけバニー
I don't want to hear it! Iiwake Bunny!
地団駄 勇往邁進 だんだん
Stamping feet, pushing forward step by step!
バニバニ だりだり マジな話
Bunny-bunny, dari-dari, seriously speaking...
どっちが好きなのよ
Which one do you like?
よそ見しないで
Don't look away!
逃げ出したいのは私のほう
The one who wants to run away is me!
通しません！反対方向
No passing! Go the other way!
WANTED！いいわけバニー
WANTED! Iiwake Bunny!
旅立とう冒険、
Let's set out on an adventure,
そしてインドアの神話へ
and towards an indoor myth.
ララララビット！！
作詞・作曲 チュタン星人
Ra-Ra-Ra-Rabbit!!
Lyrics & Music: Chutan-seijin
三色パンのスライムにビビるのが大概のマイライフ
Being scared of three-colored bread slimes is mostly my life.
1 2 3 で繋がった世界に愛が溢れ出す
Love overflows into a world connected by 1, 2, 3!
8ビットに感じるドキドキ 次のラブじゃダメですか？
My heart thumps in 8-bit, is the next 'love' no good?
運ゲー状態 ふざけんじゃないわ レベルアップして超えてやるわ
It's a game of luck, don't mess with me! I'll level up and overcome it!
夢に見てるファンファーレの音
The sound of the fanfare I've dreamed of!
離陸して 彗星 彗星 ぶっ飛ばそう 手紙もロマンスの過程
Take off! Comet, comet, blast off! Even letters are part of the romance process.
何万回 小さなビットに でっかい愛を更新中
Tens of thousands of times, updating huge love into tiny bits.
ちょっと沼っても許してね？ いつだって愛は非効率
Forgive me if I get a bit stuck? Love is always inefficient.
Jumping! Jumping! 跳ねるハートを捕まえておいてね
Jumping! Jumping! Make sure to catch my bouncing heart!
二兎なんて追わないで エンドになるぺこ
Don't chase two hares, or it'll be the end-peko!
...いつまでも最大級のララララビット！
...Forever the greatest, Lala Rabbit!
子丑寅卯
Rat, Ox, Tiger, Rabbit
うーらーらーらー！
U-ra-ra-ra!
うーらーらー！
U-ra-ra!
全人類兎化計画！
The Whole World Rabbit-ification Project!
作詞・作曲・編曲：前山田健一
Lyrics, Music, & Arrangement: Kenichi Maeyamada
主食は糖度の高い人参とするぺこ
Staple food shall be high-sugar carrots, peko
公用語はぺこ語で統一するぺこ
Official language shall be Pekolese, peko
移動はいつでもうさぎ跳びで行くぺこ
Movement shall always be by rabbit hop, peko
うーん、それはしんどいから下書きするぺこ
Hmm, that's tiring, so I'll just draft it, peko
人類爆誕数千年 進化しちゃった20XX
Humanity's birth thousands of years ago, evolved to 20XX
地球もヒーヒー言ってるし なんか雰囲気悪くない？
The Earth is gasping, doesn't the vibe feel bad?
ここはおひとつ人間卒業 みんなうさぎになっちゃって
How about graduating from being human and all becoming rabbits?
むずいことはコネコネしちゃって 突きでも持ちでも搗きましょうや
Let's knead the hard stuff and pound some mochi
さあ、人間共、今こそうさぎになるのだ！
Now, humans, it is time to become rabbits!
あはははは！
Ahahaha!
ぴょんぴょんぴょぴょぴょんぴょんぴょん
Pyon pyon pyo-pyo pyon pyon pyon
未来飛び出せ！
Jump into the future!
足元も確かめず跳んだその先で待ってるよ
I'm waiting for you where you jumped without looking at your feet
ぴょんぴょんぴょぴょぴょんぴょんぴょん
Pyon pyon pyo-pyo pyon pyon pyon
思い切りジャンプしたんだ
I took a big jump
大気圏も余裕で突破
Easily breaking through the atmosphere
宇宙の皆様こんにちはー！
Hello to everyone in space!
らーらららーらら ぺこーら ぺこーら ぺこーら
La-lalala-lala Pekora Pekora Pekora
らーらららーらら ぺこーらーーーーー！
La-lalala-lala Pekoraaaaa!
寂しすぎたら死んじゃう生き物さ
They're creatures that die if they're too lonely
だから一緒にいようね
So let's be together
約束だぺこ
It's a promise, peko
ぴょんぴょんぴょぴょぴょんぴょんぴょん
Pyon pyon pyo-pyo pyon pyon pyon
未来飛び出せ！
Jump into the future!
足元も確かめず跳んだその先で待ってるよ
I'm waiting for you where you jumped without looking at your feet
ぴょんぴょんぴょぴょぴょんぴょんぴょん
Pyon pyon pyo-pyo pyon pyon pyon
思い切りジャンプしたんだ
I took a big jump
時空さえも歪めてなんぼ
Warping space-time is what it's all about
未来の皆様こんにちはー！
Hello to everyone in the future!
うーらーらーらー！
U-ra-ra-ra!
うーらーらー！
U-ra-ra!
全人類兎化計画！
The Whole World Rabbit-ification Project!
あはははは！
Ahahaha!
ぺこーら24 Special Live
Pekora 24 Special Live